Hey, what's up guys?
So today I'll be breaking down this beard ad for you
and as always, by the end
of the video you'll have a recipe for a winning ad.
You can replicate this for any product
and it is going to work super well.
So let's begin.
If you're rock. So they start with this visual hook.
It is just some text and a emoji to create text like this.
You can use the TikTok template to create exactly this.
And for the video, they're using a guy with a full beard
and he's using one of their products.
And what they have done is they have sped up the video
to make it more visually interesting.
So these are some of the basic video editing techniques
you can use in your ads.
Instead of keeping it at a normal speed, they speed it up
to make it more interesting.
If you're rocking Apache Beard, I'm sorry,
but you look like a high schooler
And now they have a audio hook or a script hook.
This hook, it is directed more towards the pain point is,
oh, if you're rocking a Apache beard,
you look like a high schooler.
The hook is really creative
and the shots they use is just this girl talking
and they insert one B roll hair,
which is also visually interesting to watch.
Is this guy with the Apache Beard exactly
what she's talking about.
And now next she's going to introduce the product.
My advice is getting on the Beard Club, the beard.
So how they're introducing the product is, oh,
my advice is to get on the Beard Club.
So they introduce the product real quick.
This is a short ad.
Everything is super snappy In just eight seconds,
we had a visual hook, we had a script hook.
They describe the pain point
and they describe the solution real quick.
The Beard Club has growth kits
that will fill in that patchy beard.
And now her, she gives the solution that, oh,
this was our product, our brand.
It has growth kits that is going
to fill in your patchy beard.
And this shot exceptionally, I love this is something
that is being super creative with ads.
It just instantly makes you go out. What?
What does that short? So it is this guy,
he has a bandaid on his face and he removes it
and it has the word patchy in it
and inside it like this is being creative.
All their growth products work together
to stimulate new hair growth.
It comes with a derma roller growth oil
and vitamins to get you looking right.
And now she just described all the
features that the product has.
And one thing you might have noticed is she switched
locations where she was filming.
So before she was filming at this room
and now she's in the kitchen.
So this is a technique that a lot of people use,
not just in ads, but in any talking head content is if you
are constantly switching camera angles,
if you're constantly switching locations, it is
so much better for retention and it adds another layer
or dimension in your video.
And the shot she used in the features is this first shot
of the guy using the product
and the next shot is him being happy.
He looks with a full beard.
So it's showing, oh, he used our product
and it works really well.
So it is showing and also telling at the same time.
Then they showcase their other products.
They have this derma roller,
there's growth oil growth vitamins,
and next she's putting an affirming statement. There's
Literally no reason not to try this.
Yeah, super simple. She just goes like, oh,
there's no reason not to try this.
So she affirms on everything that she talked about before
and now she's going to go to the conclusion.
If you wanna up your beard game,
you've gotta try out the Beard Club.
Super simple. Again, if you want
to up your beard game, try our product.
One shot they used was this guy having a really good beard.
He's combining it and this is showing exactly
what the product is going to make you look like.
And the last shot is a showcase of all their products.
And then then with the logo, outro file.
The Beard club.
Yeah. So the only thing I might want
to add in this ad is I might add a text here saying Shop Now
or offer like just a clear call to action.
This ad is just under 30 seconds.
It's really snappy, it's quick to watch.
It gives you all the information
and it's evident that it worked really well for them.
And I hope you guys will be able
to replicate something like this for your products.
Okay guys, as a bonus, if you watch this far,
I have the script pulled up here
and I'm gonna show you an example on
how do use the same structure, the same script
to write a script for another product.
So let's say we want to write a script
for a men's skincare kit.
So the visual hook kit can be, actually you could,
you could use the same one for this,
but just to make my point clearer, I'm gonna do another one,
which is, let's say, oh, my girlfriend is mad
because I get so much attention everywhere we go.
So something like this, the pain point
or the hook, it can be something like, let's see, if your
skincare is non-existent, it's time to
bed, farewell to dull looking skin, dull
and tired looking skin itself.
So you have your visual hook, you have your pinpoint hook.
Now let's introduce our product.
So it can be something like, oh, meet the Alpha Glow
Skincare kit, your Go-to solution
for a flawless scale.
I'm making it really simple, really quick,
but if you dial this down,
you already have a winning script.
So the product intro we can use for
both the intro and the solution.
It says both. So I'm just gonna copy and paste this here
and let's go directly to talking about features.
Oh, the Alpha Glow skincare kit is packed
with antioxidants
and hydration to
uh, let's say combat daily pollutants,
something like this.
And if you talk about features more, oh,
it's a no first solution for the modern man.
It's easy, effective
and essential, simple and effective.
And then we need a affirming statement.
You could use the same,
there's literally no reason not to try this.
Or you could use something like, oh,
because taking care of your skin
is the ultimate power move.
We have a affirming statement
and then we just need a conclusion.
We can do something ready to
face the world with a whole new vibe.
And let's say dive into
Alpha Skincare kit
because your skin deserves
AVIP treatment.
Like in under five minutes I have a script using the same
structure, the same everything from the ad
that I just broke down for you.
And you can use this for testing.
So to summarize you, you go something like the visual logo.
My girlfriend is mad
because I get so much attention everywhere we go
for the pain point, you go like, oh,
if you don't have a skincare,
if your skincare is non-existent, it's time to bit farewell
to dull and tired looking skin.
We introduce our product, meet the Alpha Glow Skincare kit,
your go-to solution for a flawless skin.
So you describe your product, you describe what it does,
and this can be the same for product intro and the solution.
And then when you talk about features, you can go like, oh,
the Alpha Glow skincare kit is packed with antioxidants,
it's and hydration to combat daily pollutants.
It's a no for solution for the modern man.
It's easy, effective, and essential.
Then you affirm your offer.
You go like, oh, there's literally
no reason not to try this.
Or you go something like, because taking care
of your skin is the ultimate power move.
And then you conclude your whole video.
Go something like Ready to face the world with a new vibe.
Dive into Alpha Skincare kit
because your skin deserves AVIP treatment.
And at the end you can do a logo outro
and you could do a offer that, oh, black Friday, 30%
of buy now, something like this.
And in under five minutes you have a script ready to test.
Thank you so much for watching guys,
and I'll see you next time.